Guide to the Alumni Affairs Reference Collection, 1947-ongoing
University Archives Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
Alumni Affairs Reference collection 1947-ongoing
University Archives, Duke University
Duke University. University Archives
0.7 Linear Feet about 500 Items
Includes printed matter, clippings, newsletters and a history of the Alumni Association.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Alumni Affairs Reference Collection was compiled by University Archives staff from a variety of sources. This collection was extracted from a vertical file on alumni which included record and non-record materials about alumni, the Alumni Association and the Alumni Affairs office. The materials were received in mailings, either to the Archives office or to Archives staff involved in alumni activities.
Collection Overview
The collection includes reports of the Duke University National Council of the Alumni Association (1947-1964), demographic statistics about alumni, newspaper clippings, brochures, offers, and newsletters. Major subjects include the Loyalty fund, local alumni associations and clubs, travel, continuing education in the Alumni College, merchandise, and programming by regional or city-based alumni clubs.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Duke University. Office of Alumni Affairs
Duke University. Alumni Association
Related Material
Alumni Affairs Records
Duke University Archives
Alumni Collections
Duke University Archives
Contents of Collection
- Container List
  - Alumni: Demographics (Box 1)
  - Alumni Affairs
  - Alumni Association history
  - Brochures
  - Facts about Duke University, 1958
  - Leadership conferences, 1989, 2001
  - Marketing
  - Marking, Great Teachers, 1995
  - National Council, 1947-1963, undated
  - National Council, reports, 1947-1963 (incomplete)
  - Noteworthy alumni lists, 1966-1983
  - Programming, to 1989
  - Programming, 1990-1998
  - Programming, 1999
  - Programming, 2000
  - Programming, 2001
  - Programming, 2002
  - Publications
  - Clubs - Newsletters, 1950, 1965
  - Clubs - Newsletters, 1986-1988
  - Clubs - Newsletters, 1999-2001 (2 folders)
  - Half Century Club, 1971, 1972, 1975